<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Aris Launcher</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/"/>
 <updated>2018-03-08T17:38:52+08:00</updated>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <author>
   <name>Daniel Ng</name>
   <email>shinado023@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Use SLock to lock Aris</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/aris/promotion/2018/02/10/slock/"/>
   <updated>2018-02-10T00:31:43+08:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/aris/promotion/2018/02/10/slock</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Do you know you can lock Aris Launcher with lock plugin? If you don’t know, check this out:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/screenshot_lock.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;lock&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look cool right? You can download it in Aris Store or click &lt;a href=&quot;aris://pipe?id=2008&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;! And then, simply input ‘lock’ to lock it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you also know you can lock your launcher while some awesome code running in your console like this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/screenshot_slock.gif&quot; alt=&quot;lock&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look even cooler? Click &lt;a href=&quot;aris://pipe?id=2033&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to download now!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>使用锁屏指令</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/aris/promotion/2018/02/10/slock-cn/"/>
   <updated>2018-02-10T00:31:43+08:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/aris/promotion/2018/02/10/slock-cn</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;你可以使用锁屏指令来锁住Aris桌面（需要预先设置密码）。在桌面锁住之后你需要输入密码才可以进行下一步的操作（配合config中打开“不显示app历史”使用效果更佳），就像这样：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/screenshot_lock.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;lock&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;是不是很酷炫？你可以在Aris商店中下载这个插件，或者点击&lt;a href=&quot;aris://pipe?id=2008&quot;&gt;这里&lt;/a&gt;! 再然后，只要执行lock这个指令，你的桌面就可以上锁了。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;那么有没有更装逼一点的呢？有，像这样：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/screenshot_slock.gif&quot; alt=&quot;lock&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;如果你还没有下载这个插件的话，点&lt;a href=&quot;aris://pipe?id=2033&quot;&gt;这里&lt;/a&gt;下载（虽然是个付费插件，但是是可以白嫖的，选择第二个即可）。&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Aris Launcher</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/aris/guide/2018/02/10/guide-aris/"/>
   <updated>2018-02-10T00:31:43+08:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/aris/guide/2018/02/10/guide-aris</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-aris&quot;&gt;What is Aris&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To begin with, Aris is an Android Launcher where you do everything by searching, mostly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Aris is more than that. In Aris, you can connect various plugins to accomplish complex operations. For instance, if you’d like to share Maya’s phone number to Eric, in the normal case, you have to&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Launch contact book&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Find Maya&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Copy&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Back&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Find Eric&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Choose message&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Paste&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Send&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;whereas in Aris, just type&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;maya-&amp;gt;eric
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and hit ‘enter’ in your keyboard. Please note that you do not need to fully type ‘Maya’ or ‘Eirc’, whatever you want appears as the first item in the result area, which means it’s the Current Operating Object*, you can either hit ‘enter’ or use connection operator(-&amp;gt;) to connect it with any other items.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;connection&quot;&gt;Connection&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Linux, you can share data with pipe. Very much like this idea, you can use connection operator(-&amp;gt;) to connect various pipes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you type connection operator(-&amp;gt;), Aris will take the Primary Result* as input, ready for the next item you are going to connect it with. Via different plugins, you can use your phone like a real hacker. For instance, with APK plugin(available in Store), you can share your app as apk files to your friends in Whatsapp with this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;facebook-&amp;gt;apk-&amp;gt;whatsapp
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;some-basic-plugins&quot;&gt;Some Basic Plugins&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aris comes with few most basic plugins, which are: restart, clear, help, config, store, uninstall and info.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I may not need to explain what restart does since it is quite obvious. However, I may still need to explain the rest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;clear: To clear the console or, by using {plugin}-&amp;gt;clear to clear the pipe configurations if the plugin is able to be cleared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;config: To configurate Aris.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;help: To get help obviously. You can also use&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;{plugin}-&amp;gt;help
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to get help for the certain plugin(if applicantable).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;explained&quot;&gt;Explained&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instruction&lt;/strong&gt;：Any input in the input area is considered as an instruction&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parameter&lt;/strong&gt;：For Instruction&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;a p
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;p is a Parameter of a.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Component&lt;/strong&gt;：Refers to any item displayed in the result area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Result Set&lt;/strong&gt;：All available Components under any Instruction that does not include any operator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Primary Result&lt;/strong&gt;: The first Component under any Instruction that does not include any operator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plugin&lt;/strong&gt;：A Plugin is the executable unit, which contians one or more Components. For instance, the Application Plugin contains all applications in your phone. Any single application is a Component, whereas the Clear Plugin contains only one Component, which is Clear itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compatable Plugin&lt;/strong&gt;：A Plugin that contains multiple Components&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Action Plugin&lt;/strong&gt;: A Plugin that contains only one Component&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Full Plugin&lt;/strong&gt;：A Compatable Plugin that requires a certain Component to enable all the other Components it contains. For instance, the Directory Plugin requires user to use Instruction ‘cd’ to enable directory search.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Execute&lt;/strong&gt;：Refers to the action when you hit ‘enter’ or click on one certain Component.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect&lt;/strong&gt;：For any Instruction comes with&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;a-&amp;gt;b
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;we call Connect b with a, where the symbol(-&amp;gt;) is the connection operator.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Use SLock to lock Aris</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/aris/promotion/2018/02/10/customize/"/>
   <updated>2018-02-10T00:31:43+08:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/aris/promotion/2018/02/10/customize</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Aris Launcher not only gives you a both efficient and cool way to use you Android, but also gives you freedom to customize it. If you’ve explored the ‘theme’ session of Aris Store. You’d probably wonder how you can fully customize your Aris. Good news for you, here’s the guide on making your Aris even cooler than it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Wallpaer/Apperance
This is the most basic and easy ways you can do to customize Aris. In case you haven’t found out how to do these settings, follow me on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Long press the empty space on the console, you will see two buttons popping up from the bottom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/screenshot_popup.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;popup&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tap on the “wallpaper” button, you can either set a background color for Aris, or select wallpaper and set it as background.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you click the “Appearance” button, you’ll see this widget displayed on the console.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/screenshot_appearance.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;popup&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you tap on the first one, text size, you will see an instruction asking you to set a text size. You can do this by entering the number of the text size then hit “enter” key on the keyboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next two, console font and result font refers to the text in the display area(as we call console), and the results displayed when you search anything, respectively, which follows up text color, where you can set the color for the text on the console. Please also note that if you’re using Aris Keyboard, this color will aslo be applied for the keyboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the last three, they refer to the results showed up when you search for the items.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Tips: If you can not find any empty space, use ‘clear’ to clear the console.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Initiating message
By default, this message will show up when you launch Aris.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/screenshot_initext_default.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;popup&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can change this message in the config page, with your personal information, some other cool hacky message, even display current weather or system information if you’ve got the plugins. To enter config page, you can either find it by typing ‘config’ or in the sliding folder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now find initiating text and edit. If you want to display a plugin in the initiating text, you can use ‘${plugin}’. For instance, if you’ve got the weather plugin, simply put ‘${weather}’ in the initiating text. Once you restart Aris, you’ll get something like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/screenshot_initext_weather.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;popup&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Text on Executing
This text will be displyed whenever you execute any item. By default, this text is set to “&lt;font color=&quot;#8B76AA&quot;&gt;$s&lt;/font&gt;”, which represents the output of the item itself. You can also use html tag to format this text.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For instance, by default, when you launch Google Maps, you’ll see this message being displayed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/screenshot_initext_google_map.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;popup&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purple text is the output of this Google Maps app. This message actually is a contaction of its package name and activity name, which allows Aris to launch this app accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Console Output
As shown in the previous screenshot, when you launch Google Maps, you’ll see the text in this format:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;[time] console.execute -&amp;gt; [text on executing]
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This can be changed in the Console Ouput column in the config. You can use ‘$t’ to display current time.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Directory</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/aris/guide/2018/02/10/directory/"/>
   <updated>2018-02-10T00:31:43+08:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/aris/guide/2018/02/10/directory</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;There are two ways to start directories search.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;input cd and hit enter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;directly input ‘cd {directory of file you need}. For instance, if yuo’d like to check directory /downloads in the root, simply use
  cd downloads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that once you’re in directory mode, do not use ‘cd’ again, which is different with Linux.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you’re in directory search mode, you will be in the root directory of external storage. You won’t be able to search any other applications or plugins under this mode, until a file is executed or ‘exit’ is executed. If the file you execute is an folder, you’ll go into that folder and you’ll be able to search all the files under that folder. The indicator area will display the current directory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can connect a certain file to another plugin, notablly, another application. After connect operation, you will be able to search all the other plugins including applications. For instance, there’s this file&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;/download/wallpaper.png
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to share this file in WhatsApp, you can do this(with 3 steps)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;cd
download
wallpaper-&amp;gt;whatsapp
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;which is equivalent to&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;cd download/wallpaper-&amp;gt;whasapp
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please also note that, you do not need to input the full folder or filer. Whenever the result you need appears in the leftmost, you can continue with your next code. In this case, your input might be&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;cd do/w-&amp;gt;wh
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Back to parent directory&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under directory mode, you can use&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;cd
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to go back to parent directory. Please note that the plugin that takes you to parent directory is ‘cd..’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###List all files and folders&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under directory mode, you can use&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;ls
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to list all files and folders&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Move file&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can move files using connection operator. For instance, use&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;cd download/wallpaer-&amp;gt;images
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to move file /download/wallpaper.png to folder download/images&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Delete file or folder&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can connect any folders or files to&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;delete
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to delete them. For instance, if you’d like to delete file /download/wallpaper.png, use&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;download/wallpaper-&amp;gt;delete
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, you can use startsWith or endsWith to delete certain files whose names start or end with certains string. For instance, if you’d like to delete all files in /download that end with avi, you can use&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;cd download-&amp;gt;endswith avi-&amp;gt;delete
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Develop scripts</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/aris/guide/2018/02/10/develop/"/>
   <updated>2018-02-10T00:31:43+08:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/aris/guide/2018/02/10/develop</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Starting from 1.1.70, Aris provides a few plugins which you can work with to develop plugins based on HTTP request. Here we’ll have a simple example on getting currency to walk you into the usage of these plugins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To begin with, type “dddddvlp” to enable develop plugins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can get currency rates for various of currencies using this API:
https://api.fixer.io/latest?base=CNY&amp;amp;symbols=USD&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So now copy this url and execute “copy-&amp;gt;post”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within seconds, the console will output&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;{&quot;base&quot;:&quot;CNY&quot;,&quot;date&quot;:&quot;2017-11-20&quot;,&quot;rates&quot;:{&quot;USD&quot;:0.15074}}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, you can connect this message to plugin JGET directly using connect operator. For instance, use&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;-&amp;gt;jget rates  then you'll have 

{&quot;USD&quot;:0.15074}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To take one further step, if you only need the value for USD against CNY, just do&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;-&amp;gt;jget USD
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is to say, the full code of getting the value for CNY against USD is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;https://api.fixer.io/latest?base=CNY&amp;amp;symbols=USD-&amp;gt;post-&amp;gt;jget rates-&amp;gt;jget usd
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now you’ve created your very first script, congratulations! So I guess you’d very like to save this script so you can check the rate once in a while. Sure can do by connecting your script with “add” and name it “usd” like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;https://api.fixer.io/latest?base=CNY&amp;amp;symbols=USD-&amp;gt;post-&amp;gt;jget rates-&amp;gt;jget usd-&amp;gt;add usd
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the script is saved, you can simply use usd to get the currency rate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let’s say you have multiple currencies to watch, then you’ll need $s as parameter and save the script so you can use it to get differenct currency rates against CNY. Now the script goes like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;https://api.fixer.io/latest?base=CNY&amp;amp;symbols=$s-&amp;gt;post-&amp;gt;jget rates-&amp;gt;jget usd-&amp;gt;add currency
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now you can use&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;USD-&amp;gt;currency 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to get currency rate of USD agains CNY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;–To be continued–&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Build your plugins</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/aris/guide/2017/07/26/arscript/"/>
   <updated>2017-07-26T00:31:43+08:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/aris/guide/2017/07/26/arscript</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;alias-and-folder&quot;&gt;Alias and Folder&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting from 1.0.90, Alias is officially part of Airs default plugin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this post, we’d assume you’ve read through the post Directory. If not, please click the link and check it out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to share the file you lately downloaded from you broswer(let’s say the folder locates in /browser/download/files) to your firends in WhatsApp, you’d probably use:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;cd browser/download/files.latest.whatsapp
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re going to use it very ofter, typing such long instruction would be unevitably painful. This is where Alias comes in. Use the following instruction to turn this long instruction into a simple word.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;cd browser/download/files-&amp;gt;latest-&amp;gt;whatsapp-&amp;gt;add dlw
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see, the trick is at ‘-&amp;gt;add’. This is what we call Alias.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, when you execute ‘dlw’, Aris will equally share the latest file in folder /browser/download/files into WhatsApp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re not sure which app you’ll be using to share this file, just save this script as ‘dll’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;cd browser/download/files-&amp;gt;latest-&amp;gt;add dll
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then share it to WhatsApp, Facebook or whatsover:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;dll-&amp;gt;whatsapp
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, you can add single app or contact using Alias. The app you just added will show up in the folder in the sliding drawer, along with a bunch of other plugins you created using Alias.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
